Guide to the UTU Records
UTU Records
- Requests for Modification (Box 116, Folder 1)
- GCA Committees by Local, Title, and Amount of Assessment by Local (Box 116, Folder 2)
- BLE (Box 116, Folder 3)
- 1976 Annual Report: Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Qualifications for Locomotive Engineers (Box 116, Folder 5)
- "Background" Vol. 23 No. 2 (Box 116, Folder 6)
- Division & Region Maps: Operations (Box 116, Folder 7)
- 1990 Directory: International Headquarters and Locals (Box 116, Folder 8)
- 1991 Directory: International Headquarters and Locals (Box 116, Folder 9)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 116, Folder 10)
- Research and Agreements (Box 116, Folder 11)
- Federal Register Part II DOT, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 12)
- The National Alcoholism Treatment Center Directory 1982-83, 1982-1983 (Box 116, Folder 13)
- Misc. "Background" (Box 116, Folder 14)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 116, Folder 15)
- UTU Grievance Handling by Rail Local Chairpersons (Box 116, Folder 16)
- Railroads and Productivity: A Matter of Survival, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 17)
- Trains and the Men Who Run Them (Box 116, Folder 18)
- Productivity: Keeping Railroads on Track (Box 116, Folder 19)
- Lifeline (Box 116, Folder 20)
- Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1968 (Box 116, Folder 21)
- Uniform Code of Safety Rules, 1971 (Box 116, Folder 22)
- Gifts With a Railroad Motif (Box 116, Folder 23)
- Transportation Market in US Projected to 1990, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Field Manual (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Council Railroad Employees, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Personal Effects (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Personal Effects of Dan Collins (Box 117, Folder 5)
- Misc. "Background" (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Magazines (Box 117, Folder 7)
- Railroad Safety Coloring Book (Box 117, Folder 8)
- Correspondence (Box 117, Folder 9)
- Tri-State High Speed Rail Study (Box 117, Folder 10)
- Award Circulars (Box 117, Folder 11)
- News (Box 117, Folder 12)
- (Box 117, Folder 13)
- Roster of 4th Convention: United Transportation Union, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 14)
- Report of General Secretary and Treasurer, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 15)
- 1991 Report: UTU (Box 117, Folder 16)
- Fortieth Annual Report of the Mediation Board: Including the Report of the National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 17)
- A Curriculum of Study for Professional Practitioners of U.S. Railroad Employee Assistance Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- News Papers/ Newsletters (Box 118, Folder 2)
- Proceedings of General Chair Meetings (Box 118, Folder 3)
- Benefits (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Agreements (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Correspondence (Box 118, Folder 6)
- 1975 Proceedings (Box 118, Folder 7)
- 1984-1985 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 118, Folder 8)
- 1992 Report: Board of Appeals (Box 118, Folder 9)
- 1983-85 Annual Report (Box 118, Folder 10)
- Report of General Secretary and Treasurer, 1985, 1987, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 11)
- Proceedings of 12th Annual IRC Labor Conference, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 12)
- UTU International and United States Constitutions (Box 118, Folder 13)
- 1990 Annual Report (Box 118, Folder 14)
- Time Books (Box 118, Folder 15)
  Handle with care
- Diaries (Box 118, Folder 16)
- Rules and Rates of Pay Covering Yardmen (Box 118, Folder 17)
- The Black Mystery Box Explained (Box 118, Folder 18)
- "Background" Vol. 23 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Labor Relations (Box 119, Folder 2)
- Milwaukee Seminar, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- RLEA Assignment- Alcohol- EPA (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Young- Ferguson and Associates (Box 119, Folder 5)
- Art Linkletter's Speech to NFCA, 1971 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Alcoholism Conference-1973 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- Employment Records (Box 119, Folder 8)
- Survey Questions (Box 119, Folder 9)
- Correspondence (Box 119, Folder 10)
- Negotiations (Box 119, Folder 11)
- Snell Report (Box 119, Folder 12)
- Drugs and Alcohol (Box 119, Folder 13)
- The RRB Quarterly Report (Box 119, Folder 14)
- The UTU: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow (Box 119, Folder 15)
- Seventy-Fifth Anniversary: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1883-1958 (Box 119, Folder 16)
- Agreement, 1978 (Box 119, Folder 17)
- Colony Rail (N.E.) (Box 120, Folder 1)
- RR Benefits and SS (Box 120, Folder 2)
- UN- Syracuse Right to Strike (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Fannie Rae Plan- for Northeast (Box 120, Folder 4)
- Discipline (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Article 1 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- Article 2 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- Article 5 (Box 120, Folder 8)
- Article 6 (Box 120, Folder 9)
- Article 7 (Box 120, Folder 10)
- Article 8 (Box 120, Folder 11)
- Article 9 (Box 120, Folder 12)
- Article 11 (Box 120, Folder 13)
- Article 12 (Box 120, Folder 14)
- Article 13 (Box 120, Folder 15)
- Article 14 (Box 120, Folder 16)
- Article 16 (Box 120, Folder 17)
- Article 17 (Box 120, Folder 18)
- Article 19 (Box 120, Folder 19)
- Article 20 (Box 120, Folder 20)
- Article 21 (Box 120, Folder 21)
- Article 21A (Box 120, Folder 22)
- Article 29 (Box 120, Folder 23)
- Article 31 (Box 120, Folder 24)
- Article 33 (Box 120, Folder 25)
- Article 35 (Box 120, Folder 26)
- Article 36 (Box 120, Folder 27)
- Article 38 (Box 120, Folder 28)
- Article 40 (Box 120, Folder 29)
- Article 41 (Box 120, Folder 30)
- Article 45 (Box 120, Folder 31)
- Article 47 (Box 120, Folder 32)
- Article 48 (Box 120, Folder 33)
- Article 49A (Box 120, Folder 34)
- Article 49 (Box 120, Folder 35)
- Article 53 (Box 120, Folder 36)
- Article 57 (Box 120, Folder 37)
- Article 64 (Box 120, Folder 38)
- Article 66 (Box 120, Folder 39)
- Article 67 (Box 120, Folder 40)
- Article 70 (Box 120, Folder 41)
- Article 77 (Box 120, Folder 42)
- Article 78 (Box 120, Folder 43)
- Article 79 (Box 120, Folder 44)
- Article 80 (Box 120, Folder 45)
- Article 81 (Box 120, Folder 46)
- Article 82 (Box 120, Folder 47)
- Article 84 (Box 120, Folder 48)
- Article 85 (Box 120, Folder 49)
- Article 87 (Box 120, Folder 50)
- Article 89 (Box 120, Folder 51)
- Article 91 (Box 120, Folder 52)
- Article 92 (Box 120, Folder 53)
- Article 93 (Box 120, Folder 54)
- Article 93A (Box 120, Folder 55)
- Article 94 (Box 120, Folder 56)
- Article 95 (Box 120, Folder 57)
- Article 96 (Box 120, Folder 58)
- Article 97 (Box 120, Folder 59)
- Article 98 (Box 120, Folder 60)
- Article 99 (Box 120, Folder 61)
- Article 100 (Box 120, Folder 62)
- Constitution Amendments (Box 120, Folder 63)
- UTU (Box 120, Folder 64)
- Correspondence (Box 120, Folder 65)
- (Box 120, Folder 66)
- Employment Records (Box 121, Folder 1)
- 1970 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- 1971 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Legal Problems in Representing Employees in the Railroad Industry (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Misc. "Background" (Box 121, Folder 5)
- GE Transportation Systems Folder (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Award Circulars (Box 121, Folder 7)
- News (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Correspondence (Box 121, Folder 9)
- Labor Management Project (Box 121, Folder 10)
- Task Force Restructuring (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Tim Mellon (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Costing- FRA Rates (Box 122, Folder 3)
- BLE vs. UTU Amtrak Loc. Firemen (Box 122, Folder 4)
- Ma. Pa. Railroads (Box 122, Folder 5)
- Employee Ownership (Box 122, Folder 6)
- Wisconsin Central (Box 122, Folder 7)
- Q+A's Larry Man Testing (Box 122, Folder 8)
- CNW Spin Offs (Box 122, Folder 9)
- P+LE, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 10)
- CNW Abandonment (Box 122, Folder 11)
- Restructuring ICG (Box 122, Folder 12)
- Mid South (Box 122, Folder 13)
- Chicago Central-Pacific (Box 122, Folder 14)
- ICG (Box 122, Folder 15)
- Aircraft Mechanics Fraternal (Box 122, Folder 16)
- Paducah and Louisville (Box 122, Folder 17)
- Conrail (Box 122, Folder 18)
- Amtrak- Pass Policy (Box 122, Folder 19)
- USRA (Box 122, Folder 20)
- Opposition- Barge (Box 122, Folder 21)
- Misc. (Box 122, Folder 22)
- Conrail Labor Management (Box 122, Folder 23)
- Random Testing (Box 122, Folder 24)
- Dual Basis of Pay (Box 122, Folder 25)
- Technological Change (Box 122, Folder 26)
- UTU FS-R&S Dept. (Box 122, Folder 27)
- Wage and Rules, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 28)
- Wages, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 29)
- FRA (Box 122, Folder 30)
- UTU Facts and Figures First Edition (Box 122, Folder 31)
- UTU Facts and Figures Second Edition, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 32)
- Restructuring Task Force (Box 122, Folder 33)
- BLE- 1981 (Box 122, Folder 34)
- Crew Consist Questionnaire (Box 122, Folder 35)
- Conrail- Wage and Rules, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 36)
- Conrail- Wage and Rules, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 36)